Mohammad Shadab

I am a graduate Forensic Scientist returning to work after a gap in my work history. I am interested in a job in research or IT, as I possess all the necessary qualifications for it. I am a friendly professional person who is highly adaptable to any situation. I am a certified full stack web developer with a background in Biochemistry and Advanced Cell Biology. You are guaranteed to get the best of both worlds – Biology and Technology with me.

o7540006236
mshadab16@gmail.com
mohammad-shadab-32b35ba3
madshadab

Work Experience

Bartender | July 2017 - September 2017 | Yates Bournemouth

Cocktail Bartender | May 2017 - July 2017 | Las Iguanas Bournemouth

Receptionist/waiter | August 2016 - January 2017 | Russel Court Hotel

Waiter/Bartender/Back house | October 2015 - August 2016 | Jockey Club Racecourses

Student Ambassador | September 2015 - August 2016 | Bournemouth University

Subject Specialist Ambassador | September 2015 - August 2016 | Bournemouth University

Academic Qualifications

Advanced CSS course by Jonas | May 2020 - August 2020 | Udemy NPM, SASS, Flexbox, CSS Grid, and Ultra Responsive Designs

The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp | October 2019 -March 2020 | Udemy

Full Stack Development with HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, jQuery, Git, Node, Express, EJS, REST, APIs, SQL, MongoDB, REACT, Authentication

BSc (Hons) Forensic Science | September 2015 - May 2018 | Bournemouth University

2:1 degree with a first in most modules

AISSCE (12th) | 2011 - 2012 | Kendriya Vidyalaya BEG Pune India Subjects: Biology, Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics, English

AISSE (10th) | 2009 - 2010 | K V No 2 CPE Itarsi India Subjects: Mathematics, English, Science, Social Science, Hindi

Interests

Reading Cooking

Politics
Research

TravelForensics

. Cricket

Table tennis

Additional Qualifications

Blood Pattern Analysis Certification | April 2018 | Bournemouth University

Awarded on successfully completing the blood pattern analysis awareness course.

Global Talent Award | June 2017 | Bournemouth University

Awarded by Hon. Vice Chancellor on completion of Global Mindset, Global Heartset and Global Skillset Modules.

Debates Champion | 2016 - 2017 | Student Union Bournemouth University

Organiser of important debates held at the University; Panel speaker at the 'Healthcare in the UK' debate.

Student Rep | 2015 - 2018 | Bournemouth University

Democratically elected (annually) by my peers to represent our class at the Student Union as their leader/speaker for 3 consecutive years.

Subject Specialist Ambassador | 2015 – 2016 | Bournemouth University

Part of a two-person team selected out of 700 applicants to create and deliver an interactive workshop. Our aim was to visit various schools in South West England and get young students interested in a career in forensic science.